<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Good Kid, Hack City</title><description>A journey</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.7</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 03:24:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>The Basics</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Hi.  I started a blog.  Surprised?  Me too.  But I told myself I'm going to jump into this thing with two feet.  Here's my best effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what"&gt;What?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved to San Francisco to attend Hack Reactor, an accelerated learning program designed to equip me with the required tools to be&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/first-for-everything/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">23c3b709-c246-439e-a693-e82c0017fb87</guid><dc:creator>Adam Grimm</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 02:51:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hi.  I started a blog.  Surprised?  Me too.  But I told myself I'm going to jump into this thing with two feet.  Here's my best effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what"&gt;What?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved to San Francisco to attend Hack Reactor, an accelerated learning program designed to equip me with the required tools to be a software engineer.  Some of those tools involve engineering software.  One of those tools is, apparently, blogging.  So this is that blog.  I intend to write about stuff I learn in and out of class.  Hopefully not too much personal stuff, for everyone's sake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="who"&gt;Who?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adam Tobias Grimm.  Born 15 November 1986.  Caucasian male from the Midwest.  Studied Chemical Engineering at Washington University in Saint Louis.  Employed in that field 2008-2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm a Scorpio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="why"&gt;Why?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="http://blog.codinghorror.com/the-one-thing-every-software-engineer-should-know/"&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;, to give myself the best shot at my potential career in software development, I need to market myself.  This is a new paradigm for me (or at least, buying into it is new to me) but lots of things are new right now so why not this?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="when"&gt;When?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All day, every day.  &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>